Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6 5583/6
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Commonwealth Edison, 1927-1929 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Edison Round Table, 1927-1929 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19 (1927) - v.21 (1929). Bound volume.
- Commonwealth Edison, 1930-1938 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Edison Round Table, 1930-1938 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22 (1930) - v.30 (1938). Bound volume.
- Commonwealth Edison, 1939-1944 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Edison Round Table, 1939-1944 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31 (1939) - v.36 (1944). Bound volume.
- Commonwealth Edison, 1945-1948 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Edison Round Table, 1945-1948 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.37 (1945) - v.40 (1948). Bound volume.
- Commonwealth Edison, 1949-1951 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Edison Round Table, 1949-1951 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.41 (1949) - v.46 (1954). Bound volume.
- Massachusetts Division of Employment Security, 1974-1979 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Employment Review, 1974-1979 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    Author: Occupational Industry Research Department
    Notes: v.1 (1974) - v.6 (1979). Bound volume.
- Migrant Legal Action Program, 1974; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: MLAP Monthly Report, 1974; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1974:Jan.) - v.3:no.11 (1974). Bound volume.
- Fieldcrest Mills. Marshall Field and Company., 1947-1953 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Mill Whistle, 1947-1953 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Author: Fieldcrest Mills. Marshall Field and Company.
    Notes: v.6:no.7 (1947:Oct. 13) - v.9:no.24 (1953: July 20). Bound volume.
- American Communications Association, 1939-1945 (Box 45A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: ACA News, 1939-1945 (Box 45A, Folder 1)
    Author: American Communications Association
    Notes: v.1 (1939) - v.6 (1945). Bound volume.
- American Communications Association, 1946-1951 (Box 45A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: ACA News, 1946-1951 (Box 45A, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7 (1946) - v.12 (1951). Bound volume.
- U. S. War Production Board., 1943-1945 (Box 45B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Labor Management News, 1943-1945 (Box 45B, Folder 1)
    Author: U. S. War Production Board.
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1943:July) - v.4:no.24 (1945:Sept.). Includes Index. Complete run. Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1953-1954 (Box 45B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1953-1954 (Box 45B, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.3878 (1953:Jan. 2) - no.3982 (1954:Dec. 31). Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1955-1957 (Box 46A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1955-1957 (Box 46A, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.3983 (1955:Jan. 7) - no.4100 (1957:Apr. 12). Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1957-1958 (Box 46A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1957-1958 (Box 46A, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.4101 (1957:Apr. 19) - no.4189 (1958:Dec. 26). Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1959; Publication (Box 46B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1959; Publication (Box 46B, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.4190 (1959:Jan. 2) - no.4241 (1959:Dec. 25). Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1960-1961 (Box 46B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1960-1961 (Box 46B, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.4242 (1960:Jan. 1) - no.4296 (1961:Jan. 5). Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1961; Publication (Box 46B, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1961; Publication (Box 46B, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.4297 (1961:Jan. 13) - no.4347 (1961:Dec. 29). Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1962; Publication (Box 47A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1962; Publication (Box 47A, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.4349 (1962:Jan. 12) - no.4399 (1962:Dec. 28). Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1963; Publication (Box 47A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1963; Publication (Box 47A, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.4400 (1963:Jan. 4) - no.4451 (1963:Dec. 27). Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1964; Publication (Box 47A, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1964; Publication (Box 47A, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.4452 (1964:Jan. 3) - no.4503 (1964:Dec. 25). Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1965; Publication (Box 47B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1965; Publication (Box 47B, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.4504 (1965:Jan. 1) - no.4556 (1965:Dec. 31). Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1966; Publication (Box 47B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1966; Publication (Box 47B, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.4557 (1966:Jan. 7) - no.4608 (1966:Dec. 30). Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1967; Publication (Box 47B, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1967; Publication (Box 47B, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.4609 (1967:Jan. 6) - no.4660 (1967:Dec. 29). Bound volume.
- National Association of Corporation Schools, 1914; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1914; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Author: National Association of Corporation Schools
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1914:Mar.)-v.1:no.7 (1914:Sept.). Bound volume.
- National Association of Corporation Schools, 1914-1915 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1914-1915 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.1:no.7 (1914:Sept.)-v.2:no.12 (1915:Dec.). Bound volume.
- National Association of Corporation Schools, 1916; Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1916; Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3 (1916). Bound volume.
- National Association of Corporation Schools, 1917; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1917; Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.4 (1917). Bound volume.
- National Association of Corporation Schools, 1918; Publication (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1918; Publication (Box 48, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.5 (1918). Bound volume.
- National Association of Corporation Schools, 1919; Publication (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1919; Publication (Box 48, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.6 (1919). Bound volume.
- National Association of Corporation Schools, 1920; Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1920; Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.7 (1920). Bound volume.
- Engineers Joint Council, 1953-1964 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Engineering and Scientific Manpower Newsletter, 1953-1964 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    Author: Engineering Manpower Commission
    Notes: no.44 (1953)-no.138 (1964). Bound volume.
- National Society of Professional Engineers, 1956-1967 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Engineering Employment Practices Newsletter, 1956-1967 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    Author: National Society of Professional Engineers
    Notes: v.1 (1956)-v.12 (1967). Bound volume.
- Engineers Joint Council, 1965-1977 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Engineering Manpower Bulletin, 1965-1977 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.1 (1965)-no.34 (1977). Bound volume.
- Federal Reserve Club of New York, 1949-1956 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Fed, 1949-1956 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    Author: Federal Reserve Club of New York
    Notes: v.1:no.9 (1949:Aug. 3)-v.8:no.16 (1956:Nov. 7). Incomplete: many issues missing. Bound volume.
- Federal Reserve Club of New York, 1934-1937 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Federalist, 1934-1937 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.25 (1934)-v.31 (1937). Bound volume.
- Federal Reserve Club of New York, 1937-1940 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Federalist, 1937-1940 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32 (1937)-v.37 (1940). Bound volume.
- Federal Reserve Club of New York, 1940-1942 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Federalist, 1940-1942 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.38 (1940)-v.43 (1942). Bound volume.
- Federal Reserve Club of New York, 1942-1945 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Federalist, 1942-1945 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.44 (1942)-v.50 (1945). Bound volume.
- Federal Reserve Club of New York, 1945-1946 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Federalist, 1945-1946 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.51 (1945)-v.54 (1946). Bound volume.
- Federal Reserve Club of New York, 1946-1949 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Federalist, 1946-1949 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.55 (1946)-v.59 (1949). Bound volume.
- Hamilton Watch Company, 1925-1931 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Hamilton Watch Words, 1925-1931 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    Author: Hamilton Watch Company
    Notes: v.1 (1925)- v.8 (1931). Bound volume.
- John B. Stetson Company, 1919-1920 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Hat Box, 1919-1920 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    Author: John B. Stetson Company
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1919:Nov.)- v.2:no.3 (1920:Dec.). Bound volume.
- John B. Stetson Company, 1921-1926 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Hat Box, 1921-1926 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3 (1921)-v.7 (1926). Bound volume.
- John B. Stetson Company, 1926-1931 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Hat Box, 1926-1931 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8 (1926)-v.12 (1931). Bound volume.
- Prudential Insurance Company, 1919-1925 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Home Office News, 1919-1925 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Author: Prudential Insurance Company
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (1919)- v.8;no.2 (1925). Bound volume.
- Prudential Insurance Company, 1927-1934 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Home Office News, 1927-1934 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.10 (1927)-v.16:no.9 (1934). Bound volume.
- Prudential Insurance Company, 1935-1940 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Home Office News, 1935-1940 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.16:no.10 (1935)-v.21 (1940). Bound volume.
- Illinois Central System, 1922-1923 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Illinois Central Magazine, 1922-1923 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    Author: Illinois Central System
    Notes: v.11 (1922/1923). Bound volume.
- Illinois Central System, 1923-1924 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Illinois Central Magazine, 1923-1924 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.12 (1923/1924). Bound volume.
- Illinois Central System, 1924-1925 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Illinois Central Magazine, 1924-1925 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.13 (1924/1925). Bound volume.
- Illinois Central System, 1925-1926 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Illinois Central Magazine, 1925-1926 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.14 (1925/1926). Bound volume.
- Illinois Central System, 1926-1927 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Illinois Central Magazine, 1926-1927 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.15 (1926/1927). Bound volume.
- Illinois Central System, 1927-1928 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Illinois Central Magazine, 1927-1928 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16 (1927/1928). Bound volume.
- Illinois Central System, 1928-1929 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Illinois Central Magazine, 1928-1929 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17 (1928/1929). Bound volume.
- Illinois Central System, 1929-1931 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Illinois Central Magazine, 1929-1931 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18 (1929/1930)-v.19 (1930/1931). Bound volume.
- Illinois Central System, 1931-1935 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Illinois Central Magazine, 1931-1935 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.20 (1931/1932)-v.23 (1934/1935). Bound volume.
- Illinois Central System, 1935-1938 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Illinois Central Magazine, 1935-1938 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.24 (1935/1936)-v.26 (1937/1938). Bound volume.
- Illinois Central System, 1938-1942 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Illinois Central Magazine, 1938-1942 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.27 (1938/1939)-v.30 (1941/1942). Bound volume.
- Illinois Central System, 1942-1945 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Illinois Central Magazine, 1942-1945 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31 (1942/1943)-v.33 (1944/1945). Bound volume.
- Illinois Central System, 1945-1949 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Illinois Central Magazine, 1945-1949 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34 (1945/1946)-v.37 (1948/1949). Bound volume.
- Illinois Central System, 1949-1953 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Illinois Central Magazine, 1949-1953 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.38 (1949/1950)-v.41 (1952/1953). Bound volume.
- Brooklyn Electric; New York Edision; United Electric Light and Power; New York and Queens Electric Light and Power; Yonkers Electric Light and Power, 1929-1932 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Metropolitan Electric Topics, 1929-1932 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    Author: Brooklyn Electric; New York Edision; United Electric Light and Power; New York and Queens Electric Light and Power; Yonkers Electric Light and Power
    Notes: v.1 (1929)-v.4 (1932). Bound volume.
- Industrial Relations Counselors, 1927; Publication (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Monthly Bulletin of Industrial Relations Counselors, Inc., 1927; Publication (Box 54, Folder 3)
    Author: Industrial Relations Counselors
    Notes: August,1927-December,1927. Bound volume.
- Railroad Retirement Board, 1940-1942 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Monthly Review of the Railroad Retirement Board, 1940-1942 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    Author: Division of Reports and Information Service
    Notes: v.1 (1940)-v.3 (1942). Bound volume.
- Railroad Retirement Board, 1943-1945 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Monthly Review of the Railroad Retirement Board, 1943-1945 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.4 (1943)-v.6 (1945). Bound volume.
- Railroad Retirement Board, 1946-1948 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Monthly Review of the Railroad Retirement Board, 1946-1948 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.7 (1946)-v.9 (1948). Bound volume.
- Railroad Retirement Board, 1949-1951 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Monthly Review of the Railroad Retirement Board, 1949-1951 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10 (1949)-v.12 (1951). Bound volume.
- Railroad Retirement Board, 1952-1954 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Monthly Review of the Railroad Retirement Board, 1952-1954 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.13 (1952)-v.15 (1954). Bound volume.
- Railroad Retirement Board, 1955-1957 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Monthly Review of the Railroad Retirement Board, 1955-1957 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.16 (1955)-v.18 (1957). Bound volume.
- Railroad Retirement Board, 1958-1960 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Monthly Review of the Railroad Retirement Board, 1958-1960 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.19 (1958)-v.21 (1960). Bound volume.
- Railroad Retirement Board, 1961-1962 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Monthly Review of the Railroad Retirement Board, 1961-1962 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.22 (1961)-v.23 (1962). Bound volume.
- Railroad Retirement Board, 1963-1964 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Monthly Review of the Railroad Retirement Board, 1963-1964 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.24 (1963)-v.25 (1964). Bound volume.
- Railroad Retirement Board, 1967-1968 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Monthly Review of the Railroad Retirement Board, 1967-1968 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.28 (1967)-v.29 (1968). Bound volume.
- Proctor and Gamble, 1940-1953 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Moonbeams, 1940-1953 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Author: Proctor and Gamble
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1940:Aug.)- v.14:no.3 (1953:Aug.). Bound volume.
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1950-1952 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Motorman, Conductor and Motor Coach Operator, 1950-1952 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    Author: Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America
    Notes: v.58 (1950)-v.60 (1952). Bound volume.
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1953-1955 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Motorman, Conductor and Motor Coach Operator, 1953-1955 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.61 (1953)-v.63 (1955). Bound volume.
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1956-1958 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Motorman, Conductor and Motor Coach Operator, 1956-1958 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.64 (1956)-v.66 (1958). Bound volume.
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1959-1961 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Motorman, Conductor and Motor Coach Operator, 1959-1961 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.67 (1959)-v.69 (1961). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad, 1923-1925 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Mutual Magazine, 1923-1925 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Author: Mutual Benefit Association of Pennsylvania Railroad Employees
    Notes: v.9 (1923/1924)-v.10 (1924/1925). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad, 1925-1927 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Mutual Magazine, 1925-1927 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11 (1925/1926)-v.12 (1926/1927). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad, 1927-1929 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Mutual Magazine, 1927-1929 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.13 (1927/1928)-v.14 (1928/1929). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad, 1929-1930 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Mutual Magazine, 1929-1930 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.15 (1929/1930). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad, 1930-1931 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Mutual Magazine, 1930-1931 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16 (1930/1931). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad, 1931-1933 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Mutual Magazine, 1931-1933 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17 (1931/1932)-v.18 (1932/1933). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad, 1933-1935 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Mutual Magazine, 1933-1935 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19 (1933/1934)-v.20 (1934/1935). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad, 1935-1936 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Mutual Magazine, 1935-1936 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.21 (1935/1936). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad, 1936-1937 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Mutual Magazine, 1936-1937 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.22 (1936/1937). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad, 1937-1939 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Mutual Magazine, 1937-1939 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.23 (1937/1938)-v.24 (1938/1939). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad, 1939-1941 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Mutual Magazine, 1939-1941 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.25 (1939/1940)-v.26 (1940/1941). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad, 1941-1943 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Mutual Magazine, 1941-1943 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27 (1941/1942)-v.28 (1924/1943). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad, 1943; Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Mutual Magazine, 1943; Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.1-6 (1943). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad, 1944-1946 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Mutual Magazine, 1944-1946 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.7 (1944)-v.31 (1945/1946). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad, 1946-1948 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Mutual Magazine, 1946-1948 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32 (1946/1947)-v.33 (1947/1948). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad, 1948-1950 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Mutual Magazine, 1948-1950 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34 (1948/1949)-v.35 (1949/1950). Bound volume.
- National Association of Manufacturers, 1934-1943 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: NAM Industrial Relations Bulletin, 1942-1943 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    Author: National Association of Manufacturers
    Notes: no.42 (1942:Aug.)-no.48 (1943:Mar.). Bound volume.
  - Item 2: NAM Labor Relations Bulletin, 1934-1942 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1934:Oct.)-no.41 (1942:May). Bound volume.
- Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railway, 1925-1926 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: N., C., and St. L. RY. News Item, 1925-1926 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    Author: Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railway
    Notes: v.6 (1925)-v.7 (1926). Bound volume.
- Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railway, 1927-1928 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: N., C., and St. L. RY. News Item, 1927-1928 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.8 (1927)-v.9 (1928). Bound volume.
- National Society of Professional Engineers, 1967-1973 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Newsletter, 1967-1973 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Author: Professional Engineers in Industry
    Notes: v.12 (1967)- v.18 (1973). Bound volume.
- New York Central Lines, 1926-1927 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New York Central Lines Magazine, 1926-1927 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Author: New York Central Lines
    Notes: v.7 (1926/1927). Bound volume.
- New York Central Lines, 1927-1928 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New York Central Lines Magazine, 1927-1928 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8 (1927/1928). Bound volume.
- New York Central Lines, 1928-1929 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York Central Lines Magazine, 1928-1929 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9 (1928/1929). Bound volume.
- New York Central Lines, 1929-1930 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York Central Lines Magazine, 1929-1930 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.10 (1929/1930). Bound volume.
- New York Central Lines, 1930-1932 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York Central Lines Magazine, 1930-1932 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.11 (1930/1931)-v.13:no.5 (1932:Aug.). Bound volume.
- New York State Department of Labor, 1942-1944 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New York State Department of Labor. Press Releases, 1942-1944 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Author: Labor Publications Editor
    Notes: January,1942-May,1944. Bound volume.
- New York State Department of Labor, 1948-1955 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New York State Department of Labor. Special Labor News Memorandum, 1948-1955 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.3 (1948:Apr. 5)-no.55 (1955:Feb. 28). Incomplete. Bound volume.
- New York State Department of Labor, 1955-1958 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York State Department of Labor. Special Labor News Memorandum, 1955-1958 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.56 (1955:Mar. 28)-no.79 (1958:June 15). Bound volume.
- New York State Department of Labor, 1946-1947 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York State Department of Labor. Statistical Review, 1946-1947 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25 (1946/1947). Bound volume.
  - Item 2: New York State Department of Labor. Labor Market Letter, 1947; Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.26 (1947). Bound volume.
- New York State Department of Labor, 1947; Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York State Department of Labor. Statistical Review, 1946-1947 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: New York State Department of Labor. Labor Market Letter, 1947; Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
- New York State Department of Labor, 1968-1971 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: New York State Department of Labor. Weekly Labor News Memorandum, 1968-1971 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.23 (1968)-v. 26 (1971). Bound volume.
- New York State Department of Labor, 1972-1974 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York State Department of Labor. Labor News Memorandum, 1972-1974 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27 (1972)-v.29 (1974). Bound volume.
- League For Industrial Democracy, 1925-1929 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: News-Bulletin, 1925-1929 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Author: League For Industrial Democracy
    Notes: v.3:no.3 (1925:May)-v.7:no.3 (1929:May). Bound volume.
- Ebasco Services, 1945-1946 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: News Items, 1945-1946 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Author: Industrial Relations Department
    Notes: January,1945- August,1946. Bound volume.
- Society for the Advancement of Management, 1938-1941 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: News Letter, 1938-1941 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    Author: Society for the Advancement of Management
    Notes: no.1 (1938:July 22)-no.19 (1941:May 15). Bound volume.
- 5 Rail Operating Brotherhoods, 1960-1962 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: News Letter from the 5 Rail Operating Brotherhoods, 1960-1962 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    Author: 5 Rail Operating Brotherhoods
    Notes: November, 1960-January, 1962. Bound volume.
- New Jersey State Federation of Labor, 1956-1961 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Newsletter, 1956-1961 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    Author: New Jersey State Federation of Labor
    Notes: v.1 (1956)- v.6 (1961). Bound volume.
- Connecticut General Life Insurance, 1939-1949 (Box 63, Folder 7)